Mohamed Mahmoud Kosba

Cairo, Egypt | Flutter Developer | Website to check my apps

mohamed.kosba96@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/kosbaship

+20 1010152378 | WhatsApp

https://kosbaship.github.io/site/

Summary

I have almost a year of experience in **Flutter** after two years of **Android** development, and **SOLID** is not just a word for me in **Dart**, I am more than familiar with **Dio**, **RxDart**, **GetIt**, **Bloc/Cubit**, **Repository** and **Dependency Injection** pattern and also up-to-date with the mobile landscape, architectures, trends, and emerging technologies.

Projects

Cloth-Shop (Bloc/Cubit – Firebase)

This app is an online **Cloths-Shop**. Check The App Click Here

Courses-Shop (Bloc/Cubit – Dio – API – Firebase)

This app is an online **Course-Shop**. Google Play Click Here Check The App Click Here

Chatting (Firebase – ListView - Animations)

This app lets you join a **Chatting** room. Check The App Click Here

Weather (API - Location - Permissions)

This app gets current location **Weather** and any searched country also. Check The App Click Here

Experience



Flutter Developer Intern

Softagi

Aug 2020 - Jan 2021 (6 months)



Android Developer Intern

It Sharks

Oct 2018 - Mar 2019 (6 months)

Education



University of the People

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science 2018 - 2021



Udacity

Advanced Android Developer 2016 – 2018

Skills

Android Development • Android Studio • Android SDK • Flutter • Mobile Devices • Mobile Applications • Firebase • API Development • iOS • CI • RESTful API • Google Play

Military State: Exempted